Okay next is mdla manualif
Dynamic Life assurance this is the
most unique traditional life insurance because it
can be th Life or H Life or
endome premium payment period 5 10 15 20
years or during the protection period the
protection period is 20 30 to 90 years
so it can be chosen then you can
also choose the End of Coverage Period benefit
Is there no
cash value or the premium is forfeited this is
plan A or do you want the premium to be returned 100%
plan B or up liquid 100% plan C minimum
premium 5 million per year or
475,000 per month entry age 30 days
to 70 years can be added Raider
laap Life assurance plus and wif of
premium premium exemption if affected by
critical illness this product can be
used for financial protection
during the productive period inheritance preparation or
wealth accumulation next this
mdla plan choice there are plan A B and C the
death benefit is the same 100%
up the difference End of Coverage Period benefit
plan A does not exist or the
premium is forfeited plan B premium is returned
100% plan C the up is 100% liquid.  then the
coverage period for plan A
the choice is 20 or 30 years plan B 20
to 60 years and plan C can be
longer 20 to 90 years plan B
and C can be a
lifetime insurance just choose a
long coverage period next this is an example of the
MDLA premium here I present for a
40 year old man with plan A B and C and
for plan C there are two up options
both 1 M the premium payment period is the
same 10 years the coverage period
for the three is 30 years while the
last one is 70 years well the premium per
year is for plan A 13 R5 million
so pay 10 years covered for 30
years plan A End of
Coverage benefit there is no if you
don't like the premium being forfeited then
add a little premium then it becomes
plan B and all the premiums will be returned
after the contract ends which is 30 years
then age 40 means age 70 will
receive yes if still alive amounting to
159.6 million want a bigger
benefit then choose PL c  the premium is
bigger, right, which is
32.28 million per year for 10 years, it
will definitely be paid out 1 M whether you die
in 30 years or are still alive
after 30 years, namely at the age of 70 years,
then you can also choose this PL C
for life, choose the
longest coverage period, which is
70 years, 40 + 70 is 110 years, you could
say that almost no one
reaches the age of 110 years, so the up is
definitely paid out, right, the premium is
18.65 million, the total deposit for 10 years is
r16 million, you will definitely get 1 M for the heirs
Well, for plan A, this one is in the
term Life category, plan B, this one is
also in the term Life category, but Rop Return of
premium Ren, whose coverage period is
30 years, is in the endowment category
because there are two benefits, protection benefits
and life benefits, then plan C,
because it is for life, is in the
whole life category. Okay, those are some examples of
MDLA premiums